First of all, we are in this IDE
that is, when you're inside it
You see, if you don't have such a folder
you're just randomly coding
You put everything under one folder
So you see, I'm currently selecting the outermost layer, right?
If I create a new file
it will create a new file at the outermost level
For example, here I name it 112233 dot
MD, right
You see, it's placed right at this location
then if I delete it
just right-click to delete it, right?
OK it's deleted
What if I create a new file in the outermost layer
Hahaha, click MD
OK it's placed here
You see, it will be very messy
So what we need to do is let me take a look
delete it
the section below is also deleted
So what we need to do is to standardize it.
So why do we need standardization?
The number of files keeps increasing
You won't be able to find things
Then, the content generated by AI
you don't know which folder to put it under
it's very easy to lose track
Then, if some project background materials are scattered everywhere,
You need to from this location
it's like you drag something over here
drag it into the AI
When you drag something into here
you can't drag it accurately
You don't know whether it's been dragged or not
Because there are some Chinese names
For example, let me give you an example
you should all know
for this ANTIGRAVITY
There's one more thing that hasn't been updated
when you drag a Chinese text over
its path
It did something called, what's it called... a translation
it performed a translation
So you see I dragged a file in
He didn't know which file it referred to
whether it's this name or that name
So his understanding of Chinese still has some issues in this regard
So in conclusion
The more standardized your files are
you will find it more convenient to do this in the future
And, um, this standardized file structure
you can even reference git
that is, if you have something you want the team to use
this file needs to be shared with both Me Zhang San
and also for my Li Si to use
and then it can be used by the members in my team
Then you can use git to manage it
After managing it
then you can upload it to git
then he can pull it down
Then you can collaborate
This is version management
Then
What can we do
The first thing is that the AI can understand what this folder means
For example, this is called context
it's the context, so he knows
This might contain some contextual information.
then this DOS knows that files are stored here
or some materials
Then here we have the PRD
and then there is a drafts
he knows this is a draft
There is a templates here
it's just called English
It doesn't necessarily have to use this one
Actually, it doesn't necessarily have to be in English.
You can use Chinese pinyin or anything
Because AI is very good at understanding this kind of thing
it's just that in English
These few words are not difficult
so I used English
I think this is more standardized.
Then, some reusable resources can be centralized together
That is to say, I often need to write some prompts
Then I'll create a folder for prompts
and then all the prompts I've collected
related to this project
I'll just throw them all in
Then I put all the template-related stuff
I'll just throw them all into the templates folder, okay
I put them all in here
so it can better manage my files
So, personally, I would highly recommend a folder structure
What is the structure?
Let me explain to you
First of all, the project name goes without saying
What is the name of your project?
The project name is called Advanced and Practical Use of IDE for Product Managers
This is the project name, right?
I've closed all these things
All of these can be closed here
OK this is the first one
This is the project name
Then the first folder is dot agent
This dot agent will have the following content underneath it
One is lose
one is WALKFS
Actually, what else does it have?
It's something that has been around recently.
It also has one, let me directly create a new one for everyone
I'll manually craft it
Let's just call it skills, right?
Why
Because you open this thing called, uh, this thing called ANTIGRAVITY
its help manual
There is a section here called, uh, the release change log
It has a changelog, right?
The update log on January 13th
he tells you
it supports this agent skills
He mentioned that the agent skills were placed here
Then this agent skills he tells you
It is now available
it already supports it, right
Then after it's supported
Just go and check out the help manual
Be sure to check the official help manual
You haven't been exposed to this new thing, right?
Why
Zhang San understands this very well
Li Si doesn't understand this thing
Because you need to refer to the help manual
You should look at the official stuff
Don't watch those bloggers
to interpret some second-hand Messages
Just go check the official website directly
The official website has everything, right?
Where does his information come from
He also gets it from this official website.
Let's just look here directly
So here, you see the skills are placed in this location
Then, it's okay if you don't understand
We have immersive translation available
Then open this immersive translation
You see, it tells you
I have done this so-called translation content
dashed line
He made a Chinese-English comparison
You see, he's now telling you
he has this support for this skill
Now, this skill has two types
One is placed in what's called the workspace
it is placed in the workspace
one is placed globally
For the global scope, it is placed in the root directory under your installation directory
If it's called a workspace
You can see it's placed under the agent in your project file
then skills
and then there is a skill folder below
this is the skill folder
Then this place will give you a directory
You see, create a skills folder under the agent
then create a folder called my skill here
then create another SKT.md file below
So I'll create another folder here
This is called my skill
Note that if multiple English words need to be concatenated
it is recommended to use this called a hyphen
rather than an underscore
that's what it means
Then below
Then you see you're inside now
right
Then you click on 'New File'
and it's called SI
Here it needs to be capitalized
Why should it be capitalized?
because it recommends you to use uppercase
See
My skill
then skill.md
he recommends this way
Each skill requires you to have a prerequisite metadata
You don't need to worry about it
Just follow the requirements and paste it in, that's all you need to do.
Look, this is a name
is a name
It tells you that this is, uh, an SK of Me
Then there is a description here
it's a help
Look, uh, help
Of course, did it bring itself out?
It's something like
When you need to use it,
how how how
Then this is some description of it
This is a template.
OK, never mind
Look, there's something called best practices here
It will tell you how to use this skill
Here is the code review skill
and so on and so forth
then you find that you can't understand this help manual
or it's written very concisely
What should you do
You can refer to the Cursor help manual
Why
Because Cursor's help manual is very detailed
You can even compare both sides
their functions and so on
take a look
Now cos doesn't even require you to translate
He himself made this so-called multilingual version
Look at CN
And then here we have this thing called skill
skill means ability
You see, it tells you how to place this skill
It is placed under the cursor
and there is a skills
and then there's a my skill below
then this skill dot MD
You see if you're in cursor
it's not in the dot agent
It's in the cursor dot
because of different files
but you see there's no difference between .curs and .agent
You understand the meaning on its official website
you'll know where to put it
So this ANTIGRAVITY
it requires you to put it into this point agent
OK so it's not something I made up
It's called he requires you to put it here
So just refer to the official manual
The official manual tells you where its directory is placed
So you don't need to look at any second-hand information
what to check
Where should this be placed
Why can't I put it right?
Then some friends said they didn't understand what this 'skill' was.
and these basics and so on
It's very simple
it means you've missed the previous lessons
is just missing a lot
then you'll have to make it up in 2026
If you work as a product manager
If you still don't know how to use this IDE
then you won't understand any of these things
then you're done for
Then you're already very outdated
You're really outdated already
You don't necessarily have to be an expert
but you must know these things and concepts
This is the most basic requirement
OK, alright
We've already covered this
Let's go back here
Now I already have an agent
So what should be placed under this agent?
put in the skills
put WORKFS
So what are they respectively?
Let's just look at his manual
That's also fine
You see, there's this thing here called uh skills
and what is this called WALKFS
So what is lose
lose refers to the rules
The rules include both local and global rules
That means when you're chatting here
The rules will be loaded in any chat window
are all loaded into
That is to say, he needs to follow this rule
So the global rule is in this position
there is something called this customization
and there is a lose here
In this position
You see, it has a 'global' setting, right?
right
global means it's a global rule
Then, if you click on this workspace,
For example, if I write something called my rules
right
As you can see, there is a my rose here
Then this RUTH is actually an RTS for my own project.
Then I'll just pick one randomly
There is no RUTH here
Then I'll just randomly write something called
OK then save
I'll close it
Look, it's already here
It tells you that this is the project's rules
This is a rule of the project
Then someone said rules
What are the rules
I, I don't quite understand what, what is a rule
Let me explain it to you simply
For example, I wrote this here, uh
There is a project here called, uh, rose
it may not have loaded
or the name is a bit conflicting
It doesn't matter
Anyway, this is a rule
So what is the purpose of the rules?
We have already covered it in the last lesson
Let's take a look at the global rules
Look at the global rules
The content here is very simple
It means you should prioritize using Chinese when thinking
Also reply in Chinese when responding.
Actually, I'm telling myself that I need to use
The AI must follow my rules
You need to think in Chinese
then reply to me
then output these professional terminology field names in Chinese
Keep the English and field names
Wait, this part is actually typed wrong
use Chinese for the output
Then if it is
Keep the professional terms and field names in their original English form, right?
Then there should be no spaces between Chinese and English or between Chinese and numbers.
And then
code block
Jason Circle Moi are not constrained by these typesetting rules
which means he can use any language
to have spaces
with or without spaces
he can use it
Then the way of thinking is,
You need to first understand Me, the user's goal
It should be said
the user's goals and intentions
Then, when discussing the solution
then after discovering logical loopholes
You need to proactively raise and provide suggestions
Up to this point
Many people say they don't know how to write it
I don't know how to write these global rules
Actually, I don't know how to write it either.
It's very simple
Just refer to the official manual.
Look inside this cursor
Let's just look at the Cursor's rules.
There are rules in cursor
The rules of COSER
You see he puts it at the cursor
point lose
He tells you this is a project rule
If you put it in this entire team
that is the team rule
There are four types of rules here
project rules
User rules
team rules and this agent.MD
And here it will tell you
The large model between different completions
does not retain memory
and the rules at this prompt set level
It will have some persistent reusability
That is to say, this thing will be used continuously
It will be loaded in this context
Then there are project rules here
Then here are the optimal time team rules
And here are a bunch of other rules
how to import it
Just go and check it yourself
In short, just remember one thing
The rule is to tell the AI what not to do
You must follow this rule
For example, coming to my place for dinner, right
You have to wash your hands before you can eat.
This is the rule in my house
Then when you come to someone else's home
You should take off your shoes first, right?
You can't go in with dirty shoes.
This is also a rule
The AI doesn't know this rule
so you need to write it down for him
This is the rule
OK then after the rules comes the work fws
As for work fws, many people don't know what it is either
I didn't understand what it was at first either
Let me tell you what it is
You can think of it as a quick command
What is a shortcut command?
For example, I want to chat with AI now, right?
then I'm going to say to it
Oh, how can you help me with task A?
and for B, you need to do this and that
so if this is a repetitive task
then delete
and then paste it to him
Every time I have to do this operation
So what should I do
I mean, it's just a fixed action
Then I'll just call it directly
Look, I have a PRD creation here
a workflow called
I select it
it has a create pd
Where is this?
Here it is
There is this create pad in my workflows
So what is this
Isn't this just a prompt?
This workflow guides the AI to complete the PRD from requirements analysis.
then the prerequisites
Then the steps of the workflow are to understand this context
You need to reference the context in this
the project background and business logic
Then you need to organize the field list
Then you need to sort out this, do this, do this
Isn't this just a prompt?
I just packaged it into a shortcut command
and then I tell you it's called Create PRD
What else do I have?
I also have this thing called analyse business
I need to analyze the business
Analyzing the business is used for business analysis
Essentially, this business analysis is just a prompt.
It is still a prompt
It simply uses a structure called workflow
then there is a description here
Here is the content
Then you just dump all the content in here
And this is a prompt
you put it in here
Next time I need it, I can just call it up directly.
so it's a WORKFS
So in Cursor
What does he define this thing as
It defines it as a command, command
Isn't there Ctrl command on Mac computers?
See what he uses
He also uses this slash to wake it up, right?
it's this slash that wakes it up
so it's called a command
Its English name is command
Right
You see, this command is placed under your project
at the point cursor
click in the commands
So ANTIGRAVITY
It uses this thing called wind surf, right
So I said he acquired their family
It's also fine to check their help manual
Open this place, there are his dogs here, right?
Open his help manual
His help manual also mentions
You, look for it on the left side of this position
Let me check here, here, here. It's called command.
Let me see
I remember it used to be called workflow.
Because I had read its help manual before
Oh here he he he called me froze
You see, once it's opened and saved
Then he can invoke it through such shortcut commands
just use a slash
then call this workflow you've defined
it will directly activate
So you see, here it's just like Windows
In Windows, it's called control alt
and there's also one called the Windows key
Then on Mac, it's called control, option, and command.
It is such a key
So this is the definition
This is called the workforce
OK we've already covered these
Actually, it is this so-called editor
its own preset folder
Then you put the content inside it
It will read the content inside according to the rules
OK and someone said hey
Can you give a practical example of how to do this
how to use workflow
I don't think it's necessary to give this example
Because I don't have a case here
I'm telling you
It's very simple
Workflow is just a shortcut key
What does a shortcut key mean?
one-click check-in
one-click clock out
one-click download
If you go by the old way
Let me give you an example
You need to write a
You need to write a PRD
just click on TXT
This is called writing something like PRD creation
created prompt
and then paste it here
and then paste it in here
then let it generate
Now I'm using workflow
It's just a matter of editing it into a shortcut.
I just type a slash here
Just call it and you're good to go
So there's nothing profound about it
including a bunch of people online talking about that skill
There's nothing advanced about it
I don't know why they spend an hour
two hours to talk about those things
explained so generally and complicatedly
so troublesome
It's just the prompt
it just has some logic inside
or its underlying components
It can disclose progressively in a step-by-step loading manner
What was it called again?
His skills can be called token-saving
It doesn't require you to bring out all these things entirely.
It will automatically recognize which skills you have
and then call it
Then in your skills
Inside this, in my skills
You can also have something called, uh,
reference
It should be called R1
This reference contains some reference materials.
And in this place, there might also be something called a script
is a script
Yes
He simply uses this prompt to call the tools inside
and then let it execute
It's that simple
a single sentence is enough to clarify
explained clearly
What is spill
To put it bluntly, some companies just love to coin new terms
and many people enjoy studying it
and then hype it up
and then keep justifying it
they talk about a bunch of very complex concepts
Actually, in my opinion
I think as a product manager
There's absolutely no need to delve into all those many
all that blah blah stuff
Then you just ask them
You go study skill
Do you think what I said makes sense?
Do you think there's anything particularly complex about skill?
Why spend an hour
spending hours talking about this concept
Isn't it just a prompt?
It's simply about processing the raw data
then call A, B or C
That's it, nothing profound.
So I think you need to distinguish that many self-media bloggers
He's just indulging in self-satisfaction
He's bombarding you with a bunch of concepts
make you think this thing is amazing
profound
then you have to buy his course
you have to learn from him
you have to do this and that
One thing I've always told everyone
it's about demystifying it
it's just the prompt
nothing else
right
Then you're going to ask me again
how to write prompts
what makes a good prompt
As I mentioned before
I said I don't know how to write prompts either
I previously posted in my Knowledge planet
You can check out how big companies write their prompts, right?
Then, besides this, you can search for prompts here.
or front, um
Let me check, I don't have it here
Then let's call it prompts
OK there's a GITHUB
There's a repository there
Go take a look
if all else fails
Let AI write it for you
Now it's very convenient for AI to generate prompts.
There are a lot of these
Look at ANTHROPIC
and then this uh Google
and KO
and this LOVEABLE
these big companies
and so on
how their prompts are written
there are people who have compiled statistics
Just learn it
Then just let the AI analyze it and you're done.
OK, so let's summarize a bit here
up to this point
The first point is the perspective I conveyed
The first thing is that everyone needs to demystify
many self-media bloggers
They are reprocessing some content for you
one moment praising this guru, the next moment
mention that expert one moment and this the next
In the end, what you create is actually flashy without substance
It's completely unusable in your actual work
Because I have already tried it
It's not as amazing as they boast.
Then someone said I built a skills
then I asked him to produce a PPT for me
do this and that
Actually, I found a dedicated PPT-making tool for the A-level exam
or such a product
such a tool
I throw my stuff to it
can still produce the same result
You use these skills simply by providing those prompts
those templates
provide all those specifications to the AI
and then let the AI execute it
But there are some things that an IDE isn't omnipotent for
It's that simple
Why do I have to use an IDE for everything?
Why don't I just use this dedicated PPT tool?
Why can't I just use Figma to do it?
That's all fine
So this is the first point
everyone should go to may
And the second point I want to tell you is
that is, you need to learn things
You need to learn firsthand knowledge
You need to go to the most cutting-edge and latest things
You need to learn firsthand
What to learn first-hand
Look at their official website
you ask everyone
Just check these official help manuals yourself
these blogs
or these so-called DOS
Have you taken a look at it
Have you ever looked at it
Have you done any research on it, right?
Including Kshell, which is now very powerful
Even searching can be done in Chinese
You can directly search for any command here, right?
It can also support you
Um, let me see
Look at the 1commands he brought up
Yes, he is in this position
And look, there are also skills here
and also this so-called sub agent
what a sub-agent is and so on and so forth
It's all here
including what MCP is
Why bother looking at those second-hand things?
Those who specialize in such tools
clearly written out all these things for you
You just need to look at it and that's it
Just go and practice.
Don't learn too much of those second-hand information
and make it so complicated
It's not that complicated
This is the second point, okay
Let's move on
The first part is
If you use this ANTIGRAVITY,
you need to remember this dot agent
This folder must be created
is placed inside this location
There are three key elements.
rose is the rule
Let me take a look
and then this skills
then this is called WORKFWS
workflows are shortcuts
a workflow orchestration
It means doing this first and then that.
and then package it into a workflow
quick command
OK, this is to click edge
And the rest of the content is all customizable.
All are customizable
Let me briefly introduce the first one, uh
this so-called analyzed
It is an analysis
That is to say, as product managers
We often need to analyze the business
When analyzing the business,
Maybe this was generated by AI for me.
Actually, it's not necessary to use such a structure
that is to say, this data analysis process analysis
and some analyses within certain scopes, etc.
it doesn't matter
you create a folder yourself
You can put it under the ANALLIES folder
And there's another point to mention,
you are under this on underlies
You can create some other folders.
For example, what we call business requirements research
Then, we can do financial requirement research or whatever.
You can create it yourself, what should we call it
to meet Chinese
There's no need to insist on using English
make it sound all fancy and whatnot
Because you can't understand it
You won't even understand your own folders later
OK, and then this context is the surrounding text
Using context with the term 'context' might make it easier to understand
because AI can understand this term better
So here, you see, I have
I wrote something called this project background
This is the background of a project
This tells you what kind of project it is
There is a target
It has what is called a user goal
and here is a core strategy
then there is a business logic
it's just some business logic
And here there's also a glossary or something like that
I've put them all here
Do you really have to call it this name?
NO up to you
I'm just giving you a reference
You need to remember
Just put the context background here
What's the name of your company?
How many people are in your team?
What system are you working on?
What modules does your system have?
What are the functions of your system?
What is the business process of your system?
How many tables does your system have?
How many fields does your system have
All these things are background information
If you don't provide it to the AI, how can the AI know what you're currently doing?
How can it help you generate those things?
So you must provide the background information to him
so that it can understand this background information
So how much can it understand
Will he have hallucinations about some things
He can't digest it
It doesn't matter
First, get these things sorted out
deliver to them
You didn't even organize it
How would they know what you're doing?
You tell me
You are a B-end product manager
You are a supply chain product manager
How would I know what your B-end does
What exactly does your supply chain do?
I have no idea
So first, you need to sort out the background information
once and for all
just do it once
Got it
you only do it once
when you need to use it later
you can put it to use
If you're not even willing to do this
Then it's over, AI is not as amazing as you think
He is highly intelligent
But he's not as amazing as you imagine
Can he read minds?
Can he know where you are right now?
No
So we must first input the background information
So this thing is the context.
And then, this DOS can be used to store some, uh
some official reference materials
learning materials
Look, I don't even have this DOS here
It didn't generate for me
It doesn't matter
Not important
can be added by yourself
I said
except for this point H and so on
The rest can be freely improvised.
freely added
And this, this, this is called, what is this called?
Draft is actually just a rough draft
I just gave it an English name
just to make it sound more stylish
You see, I've placed some temporary conversation records here
And here I might also have some miscellaneous
or what should I call it
Or I'll take it over again
Let me rename this here
What should I call this, um
What is this called? A draft version, right?
It's fine whether you've heard of this concept or not
You can name it whatever you want
Just put it under this folder for now.
Then moving on, everyone knows this PRD
I have placed all the PRDs I generated in here
You can call it whatever you want
Call it whatever you like
I just gave it an English name
just to standardize it
Then, the prompt, right?
Then why should there be a prompt in this place
You said there's a command called WALKFS here, right?
or command
Why do I still need to write a prompt here
Because sometimes we hear others share
Today, it's said that
V mentioned this NANOBANA to me in the group chat
generate an image
This prompt is very useful
I need to write this down
Where should I note it down?
Write it down in a notebook?
Isn't this a little notebook right here?
Then just write something like nano banana, right?
Then just use this prompt or simply go with Chinese, that's fine
That's it
Then, what about this image summary style, right?
Now I understand here
This is the style of the nano banana image summary
So when should we use the workflow?
Because when there are too many of these things
when I call it up here
you will have more options here
you'll get confused
So when should you use it?
you will use it very frequently
you can just turn it into a quick command like this
If you only use it once or twice
then you can put it in the prompt
So here's a prompt library
then your prompt library
You can also categorize them for learning purposes, right
for daily study use
And then here, you can add another one for work purposes
can be used for work
As you like
These things are all customizable
and then
The last very crucial thing is
this is called templates
This templates is actually just a template
This template is extremely useful
Why is that
Because many people write PRDs
when having AI generate PRD
he will only give him a prompt saying ah
you refer to this prompt
Generate a PRD for me
But what does this PRD look like, right?
It has several structures
there are several sections
there's this and that and so on and so forth
How would he know
He doesn't know
So at this point
you need to provide this PRD template to it
you need to give him the PRD template
So who wrote this PRD template? Was it written by AI?
organize the AI properly
Back when I was in the tenth session
I haven't shared it yet
Let me explain here
So friends from the tenth episode might understand this first, right?
Look, here I have something called a B-end product
Universal PRD Template
Suitable for AI comprehension and imitation
And this is something I created myself.
This is my initial analysis
And then
I have a complete template content here
Then you can directly throw this content to AI
but to save time
I just gave you a PRD template directly
This is called a markdown code block
This is a template
We can simplify
The simplified markdown is also in this position
For example, if I want a simplified version
then I'll paste it here
So here I have, uh,
Create a new folder named MD and this will be the PRD.
then paste
Then the name we just came up with is here, right?
Then I'll just call it this name
just call it this name
Then I'll rename it
rename
Then paste it, no problem.
It's fine to name it in Chinese
all are acceptable
So this is the role and value of these templates
In addition to the PRD having this template
For example, I also have something called business process
analysis, right
Then analyze whether there is any issue with Me business process
I have a template for this business process simulation.
Me's field list also has a template
Because I need to organize it
I need to create several tables
what content is included in each field
what data needs to be organized
Then I also have this one
And also, I have a front-end style
a standardized template, right
When I give this to AI
AI will refer to this to generate my uh
This is called a file
This is a style file.
This is a style file
You can also understand it as a prompt word
or a specification, both are acceptable
In short, it tells you
After you have this AIIDE,
Essentially, it is a code editor here
plus AI chat plus file manager
Let's call it a file manager
right
Then you can perform file management on it.
This is file management
OK, that's it for now
the core file descriptions and so on below
We've already covered everything
If you've understood up to this point, type '2' in the chat
If you understood, type '2' in the chat
Why did I use such a structure
What is the inspiration behind such a structure for everyone?
and what is its value
Do you understand
type two
Ok
Then someone asked about the content generated by this IDE
then you generate this folder
Just say I have those temporary transition things here
right
He wants to use it as Me background information
I'll just modify it a bit
Do you think this has formed a standard
I'll just put it into my standard folder
Just extract it out.
You must never have a mindset
think that AI is omnipotent
I don't want to take a single step myself
I tell you it's wrong
If you do it this way
You will be extremely miserable
Currently, AI can't help you with many things.
You must start by doing some initial work first
then he helps you with it
then you can make some additions to it
make some revisions
just like this
Never think that ah
Let AI handle everything
You will be very, very passive
Sure
You put all the materials here
then let it write reading summaries for you
Quarterly summaries are fine.
No problem
Absolutely can
including putting all your weekly reports here
also can
this place
You you you
You can put your weekly report into your daily routine here
right
You can put it in the draft
You can put your so-called weekly report
Then you can put your weekly report here
then you can output a summary of the weekly report
a summary or anything like that is fine
all can be done
Everything can be done, right
This is just an idea, okay
Someone might ask about such a directory structure, right
I have to type it manually
I need to manually create something like that
Am I making it too difficult for myself?
Manual creation is actually not that difficult
Because it's just about creating folders
create files
Creating the files takes just one minute.
If you really want to cut corners
Here's a prompt
let AI generate it for you
Actually, it just refers to such a directory.
the point agent it generated for you uh
the analyzed context docs
this JSPRDS
and then this prompts
and there are templates and so on
the same
You can manually write and paste it in
or you can handle them one by one, that's also fine
So this is a prompt I'm giving you
I just happened to save you some laziness
Alright
This is what we call, uh, the second part.